This is the Peg-la-Don, and you are listening to KCPR, San Luis Obispo.
My name is Peggy Kuzimech.
I'm a first-year student from Sacramento, California, and my major is journalism.
On campus, I am involved in KCPR, which is the on-campus radio station, which kinda coincides with my journalism major.
I'm also involved with the Field Studies Club and the sorority Delta Gamma.
Being in KCPR has been a big part of my school year already as a first-year.
It just is a really good community where everyone can kind of express themselves, which is my favorite part. So being in KCPR has really given me a lot of new friends and a place where I can really be myself.
I would give the advice to first-year students that are trying to find their place: just go to meetings.
If anything is really interesting to you, go out there because college is different in the sense that no one's gonna drag you to meetings.
It's kinda you have to take the first step and get out there, and it may be hard and daunting to make friends.
But it's so worth it in the end. So I'd say just take that first step.
It's gonna be awkward at first, but you'll get to know people, and it'll be a good time.